{
    "subject": "resource/El_Topo",
    "predicate": "property/music",
    "object": "Alejandro Jodorowsky",
    "human_readable": "The music of El Topo is by Alejandro Jodorowsky.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9173682332038879,
            "question": "Is Alejandro Jodorowsky a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8302380442619324,
            "question": "What kind of work did Alejandro Jodorowsky do on the film El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7964327335357666,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that features music by Alejandro Jodorowsky?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7475565671920776,
            "question": "Who composed the music for the film El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6772485971450806,
            "question": "What is Alejandro Jodorowsky known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6771776080131531,
            "question": "Besides composing music, what else is Alejandro Jodorowsky known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4815809726715088,
            "question": "What genre of film is El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43149006366729736,
            "question": "Name a film scored by Alejandro Jodorowsky."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3978228271007538,
            "question": "Who directed the film El Topo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3169551491737366,
            "question": "What other films has Alejandro Jodorowsky worked on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music of El Topo is by Alejandro Jodorowsky.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film El Topo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film scored by Alejandro Jodorowsky.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of film is El Topo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2789_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is \"The music of El Topo is by Alejandro Jodorowsky.\" and the answer is based on the context information provided.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that the soundtrack for \"El Topo\" was composed by Alejandro Jodorowsky, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}